noral or doubts in
Mind Correct
normal skepticism number one every
[Music]
time in mind right now so for example
number
one okay Lang
honest
exercise yes
Tam market so
Z ah
[Music]
okay okay so yeah thank you guys for
being honest now but basically this is
what we call the selling sustainability
now oh my God Market can I sustain my
selling so
producer producer number
one rookies well technically we all
rookies on your first day months I would
say that these are all iPad qualifiers
but IP
qualifiers good job all
okay
the
but there is also this producer number
two producer
number number one number
[Music]
two the first 3 months iPad and
then Market saturation oh my God
saturate
Marketo producer number two do you think
it's Market
saturation producer producer
number a okay conversion actually how
you convert your sales that's the
problem producer number one sales corre
so Market
saturation and you're an iPad qualifier
first thing in mind you have a limited
Vision you widen your
perspective maximize part
work talag
anec for able to maximize your Paras
maximize no not yet Hindi PA not Hindi
PA oh see how much COI familiar withi
for Market when was the last time date
K last year
[Music]
Cofe
correct
[Music]
power
investment
insurance that is a potential market now
what's the
problem relationship with your center of
influence
no of influence correct yes see
fin plan very
[Music]
good
centers
correct
[Music]
not yet not yet not
yet
Booth are you familiar with booting yes
for sure aware
boo event for
example
evay day June
correct Compass
prospecting
Compass when you say
[Music]
Compass
okay quality cold market like for
example
LinkedIn LinkedIn
filter correct
no corporate accounts corporate
accounts very good corporate accounts
for example Group
insurance keyman
insurance buy
agreement
Rd
kasama SI ate AR back then full time na
SI arto no so nil isang healthare
provider close eight cases set for life
bang retirement amazing I think it's
amounting to if I'm not mistaken 500 to
600,000
AP
amazing to bus within
[Music]
makp after work
after
correct resell have you tried
reselling is fulltime
palen for example Market survey sa palen
sample selan from Golden nak through
palente gra recently
palen Ken
caral
palen so now tell me saturate
Market that's the problem your
perspective is
limited
perspective
[Music]
Facebook okay see producer number two
skewed Vision because in reality you
have limited
time IP
qualifier
process
basic
assment correct and
that's correct
that's the point correct the the
solution there is time commitment
calendar and
commitment by statistics H this is
2018 pention
Insurance
1.62
assum
1.6 that's 3.2
number sample that's 108 million
Filipino people
assumption working middle class and
up policy 41% that's 44.9 million
correct y 1.6 that's
3.4
41 million
insurance now I will ask you is your
Market
[Music]
saturated perspective
sked hello 41 million Filipino are not
yet
insured saturated Market lure exam 3
months in the making six sets of exam
example to
Singapore you have to review the license
your exam for 3 months and take six sets
of
exam insurance agent Singapore saturated
Market
hello
[Music]
mean
OPP okay
next the market is waiting to be reaped
it's just waiting for the
highers what you need is time to harvest
them
marketas okay
see skepticism number two
Marin
[Music]
yism
yeah if you can relate to
theis
yes okay ISS confidence correct thank
you guys
after
okay close 24K SFL 30k SFL 20K
SFL
okay
[Applause]
okay Sabi what you focus on what you
focus on expans
[Music]
okay it would translate into your
actions
[Music]
okay hard work beats Talent when talent
doesn't work hard which is
true
yes
[Music]
proud which is
true
okay I made my awareness
lied
confident Talent it's something innate
correct through hours of Mastery for
examp high Network
seller expert
manifest
okay recruitment
process
[Music]
anyone
so that's my point correct you limit
your vision limit your
perspec hello Don recruit specialist
FW HR
donr process and that's the point you
need Mastery for you to have that skill
for you to have that
skill Master specific
process are you putting effort to master
the craft and what is your level of
commitment in that kind of
Mastery see check your cash are you able
to assess
it cash
knowledge attitude skills and habits
that's actually the first assessment
that you're going
[Music]
toare
one trainings
or Market
[Music]
sales
successful K FWD MGA ini invite
Monday SI sir JoJo
negapatan nakak sir
joatan correct grade two high school
graduate branch manager
mwd consistent achiever
pry
[Music]
correct
manager correct now tell
me get
okay alers
soang okay
see skepticism number three sustainable
ba business
next
year 5 years from
now may skis
yes shamun si Mike S
bin okay Ayan thank you honesty y
talag
okay thank you
guys business model sustainabil
sustainability and
stability so how far can I go this in
this
time corporate
somehow
[Music]
[Applause]
okay correct at
least at the same time a corporate there
might be some promotion opportunities or
you can opt to move
out correct bottom line
corporate setup
secur you agree secure the
home
process business model income
potential
promotion
results correct so
[Music]
promotion
corporate
[Music]
palak
vacany
correct
vac
promotion
exit
[Music]
okay it needs a vacancy correct it needs
some
[Music]
correct it's always
results
sec grow
corporate
next sustainable B
business Tim
Arlene history
manow 26
26 correct see grow Kay
Yan grow 2017 ha guys 2017
okay 2018
promote
correct and
then
n at nag
sustainable now ask
me that's 200 aspiring leaders from the
Dragon
202 sustainable at scalable bus from
2017 to 2024 consistently promoting
leaders
o
QE sustainable
2024 perspective FWD is number three
Nationwide one
FW Tam an
fwon guys 25,000
fwps
markides that's 100 110 million
Filipinos and less than 5% Market
penetration now I'm asking you
sustainable business
scalable perspective at Target FWD this
year alone is 25,000 financial
planners yes
yes
perspective okay skepticism number
four thank you
okay
common
rationalization do you agree
mindset
okay you're comparing apples to
oranges see
tayang na Kay
Sao
10 three okay
12 rationalization
mag
fwt months three months month months
soare 10 years Mo 3
months
so that's the point your time to compare
apples to oranges 10 years 5 years 3
years in your corporate setup
versus
FW it's not
true actual concern in adjust
lifestyle for part extra income to
augment your current income so let's say
you're you're gaining 20,000 per
month FW
[Music]
10K
lifestyle correct cuz you have to reward
yourself which I'm not
[Music]
saying
for because
of
okay
Inc Coro income plus your FWD extra
income income
potential have you seen the income
potential
yesterday
okay never going to happen it's never G
to happen 300,000 per week income
part-
okaying
like
before SLE
compation okay
best create emergency
F so samp so I have this recent
full-timer I know uh you know Aris padal
Bora she's earning 90,000 as a virtual
assistant
winner I want to earn a lot for my
[Music]
family emergency
fund 3 months B 3
months
actually right after our
session
Jun was November
back expenses fix
correct to
Zally back to zero because you're
earning commissions from
FWD you're giving yourself 3 months to
sell and to
recruit income emergency
emercy happy New
Year she is recruiting and building her
teamy leader and that's the
point inome
okay starting
[Music]
now to build your emergency
f
yes 300,000 per week income yet you are
not willing to pay the price correct
there's a
disconnect
Universe Universe manifesting 1 million
a month
income h 1 million a
Monita you don't want to leave your
comfort zone correct
see sample computation sample
computation H income 22,000 commiss
8K income
30k
so
problem albra XXX y y
y okay so
never
Mals
Bita Hab
emercy
okay first month second month third
month Target after
mons
100,000 50K
that's a point
see Inc guys
so um this was my income back then inome
when I
jum income 70k per
month commissions company 11,000 Plus 6
17K + 11 28,000
pant pant
[Music]
pant
F
[Music]
opportun
okay
in
reality
bmes who were brave enough
to talaga
okay I filed for resignation income 18
47,000 that's my commissions
alone versus my 70k
because it's not going happen
[Music]
Okay
correct aware before
reigning NASA
47,000 first month as
a no that's my usual ual income as a
full timer 44 + 17 71 + 33 104 + 13
17,000
yes
yes income before 70k but my first month
income as a manager
117,000 manager full time June
2018 June 30 actually July
July 1
2018 April 2019 I gave myself 9 months
to build the team that I am
building after one year one uh April may
may may of 2019
117k income more than corporate
income one year full one year full
77,000 one year as
AO that's 127 pom
127,000 + 36 that's 163 + 32 that's 198
+ 34 that's
230 to 240,000 a month
one year as
AIT fulltime
C
okay second year as a unit
manager 138 +
paom ay k 138 + 343 that's 520 + 94
that's
610 in a month
okay
director Cons with your
manager okay
next parents or
Friends full
AK ay
Mike
okay
[Music]
H okay problem acceptance and support
from your relatives and Friends see
thank you
guys they're coming from a place of love
and concern
correct insurance agent
insurance
businessess they don't see what you see
correct
[Music]
okay actually it's the fault of the
Philippine education
systemation
system
help them see how work hard and qualify
to many FWD incentives and thingss for
example Asian
[Music]
Cru
promise
[Music]
ever
IND okay
you're able to share the successes and
WIS Asian
Cru Asian Cru
seats
that's the point normal
normal because they don't want you to
fail correct so it's
normal you share your WIS with them
that's the point okay
[Music]
clity
sheland
okay quick wigs
correct okay work hard as
silence
Bashers but let your success make the
noise that's the
point
okay
position a a a very good see your
dilemma is you're afraid to go out of
your comfort zone Jeff
[Music]
Bezos computer science H career in
computer science Wall
Street CEO Amazon so he left his
possession so Wall Street
correct s Sarah Blakeley founder spax
before sh NASA sales job office supplies
door too did she leave her position to
be a billionaire yes to be a business
owner K SI Jonah
Peretti the hington post ano before
computer science teacher
did he leave his
job
okay certified Enterprise risk manager
Singapore not in the
Philippines Singapore correct but she
left her job to be a unit manager of FWD
and now to be a branch
manager certified enterpr
manager okay
next
oh
engineer CPA project
manager did they leave their jobs
yes but did they leave their
titles CPA
Eric
opportunties
passate they were not not afraid to
leave their jobs for better
opportunities calibrate yourselves now
correct Finance
head
company after
C after
CF
correct
my after CFO Co
Sil
bact
CF
correct because of the
company abroad but he was able to leave
his job for better opportunities no Cate
again after
c
okay you're deading the insurance
profession so low rank
career oh next
[Music]
opportunities
okay
insur the
nobility oh do you see the major impact
that you can create as an insurance
professional yes if you were able to
build that
confidence because you are in a noble
profession who change people's lives
correct see so
so you have the
POS commensurate
compensation commensurate it's worth
it
compens
B worth it
no flexibility with your current
position
F
okay
fible flexibility
examp nontoxic environment super
[Music]
toxic
[Applause]
okay do you see
yourselves
[Music]
[Applause]
that's my point
corre okay Lang magay magay Ka sa stay
Ka
okay usual exit an
after mag
mag mag Tam
okay as
a no that's your
plan so 20 to 40 years
chosen
field
[Music]
correct
hello
NE FWD is a
business
correct
Years
[Music]
correct
okay
ohle oh
orial at a young young age at a young
age at a young age of
32 compy was I able to build the
business was I able to build the
business did I wait for 20 years before
I become a businessman no that's the
point what are you
waiting okay
see nobody has ever become rich by
staying as an employee and that's
a
never GNA happen
[Music]
Okay goals since you're here already be
reminded that you can achieve many
things because of W set a goal that
scares
[Music]
you like earn 1 million a month your
time would be stretched and maximized
trust me
okay okay bigger goals require more
action sample activities
full-timer fulltime for example F9 if
you're familiar no so Oriental
Dragon activities for our full
timers for full for
Oriental they're doing corporate selling
so by next week
[Music]
letteries and the
next Market
vendors
agent exciting
activities Monday agents because of
those
activities
okay limited Vision you can juggle for
now client
base Hindi correct our job also entails
client servicing at
Val
generosity okay
expected team you also give time for
your recruits okay sa one heart cannot
serve two
masters
okay
worth
it decision
okay because you will always attract
what you believe you are
worth is that your wor is that your
word oh
there's yes
or you work what you are worth correct
see
this is my passion
see okay there's two perspective and
passion okay passion
love this andion
suffering common perspective in passion
I want to do the things that I love but
sometimes the things that we love do not
coincide with the things that would help
you achieve your Financial Freedom do
you agree you
agree Financial Freedom
correct see usually passion plus higher
pay
o
you're om
there science
teacher
[Music]
correct
basketball after basketb
am1 per
G correct because you're trying to
achieve Financial Freedom
see transition
plan fulltime agents do you think they
can pursue their passion to some classic
example FJ yes FJ Google GOOG Facebook
yes
okayo he can pursue his Fitness passion
n Spartan Race
correct Financial Freedom I'll example
to
okay so I love direct okay I love films
I love movies like Malaya I would go
there to watch
Thea I cannot study
film you're an IND
FM
correct at the AG of 30 30
35 I can pursue my film hudies correct
and I create my own film
producer correct and that's what you can
do because you have Financial Freedom
and that's the point to Financial
Freedom once you Achieve Financial
Freedom you can pursue things that you
love correct say
again what if you can fast your
Financial Freedom so that you will have
time to pursue your passion is that what
I'm doing that's a
point I'm pursuing my financial freedom
but I can pursue my
passion because there's a buyout concept
for an agency partner
at
district manager
F district manager buy
compensation
figures pomot RDO as district
manager district manager
soe would have this amount of money B
out R is this a good retirement plan
yes can I pursue my passion if I have
this F of
money spin Oriental from
RB excited because R would also have
this
amount out Oriental
Dr
manct manager
I would also have this
money on top of what we are earning
now so
[Music]
imagine okay you're going to work s
years district
manager last seven can you still pursue
your passion with this amount of money
that's the question okay see Hello early
retirement pursue your passion
exite okay I love my job because
okay best office nightes ever
environment
FW if you see it with your FW
teammates person
see definition passion passion is
suffering
correct deriv from the Latin word pasio
which means
suffering
soan compassion equals suffering what
are the things that you're willing to
suffer
for
or who am I willing to suffer for let's
match on
[Music]
correct you know my
story who am I winning to suffer for
that's
fion you calibrate what's your passion
really is
correct
okay for today I would open the floor
for last skepticism that I was not able
to address do you still have skepticism
that I was not able to
address or did I make things clear for
you for you to be able to atreas your
potential
yes now yes this is my assignment to you
okay